hi welcome back you're tuned into mid
cap radar on cnbc tv 18 just a quick
look at the markets right now when we
started the show the markets were down
around 90 odd points
and right now we are seeing a slight
recovery the markets are down just 53
odd points
so we will see how it pans out in the
last one hour of trade
but let's talk about some earnings
expectations then jsw
steele will be posting results today
nigel is here to take us through the key
expectations hi nigel over to you
well for jsw we're working with a weak
set of numbers whether it's with regard
to realizations or even with regard
to volumes now if you look at the top
lines expected to degrow by closer and
37 percent
operating profit will take a harder hit
it's likely to come in down by close
down 65 percent
so margins they come to around 10 that
compares with around 18 to 20
that we normally see and they expected
to report a net loss but remember the
range is very very wide so look at the
operational performance
let's do just that then in terms of
sales volumes yes we have the production
numbers and they have indicated a big
decline
so just replicating that we're expecting
the sales volumes to see a decline of
closure on 24
or thereabouts remember capacity
utilization levels have moved from
around thirty percent around seventy
eighty percent odd towards the end of
the quarter they had a bit of a problem
because of a lot of covert cases in
karnataka itself so that's why you know
production got hampered out there
in terms of margins there'll be some
relief because raw material cost has
come in lower that's the cooking cold
cost maybe some
bit of softening in terms of fire no
cost but losses continue at their
subsidies so that's what hurts them
and negative operating operating
leverage as well a bit up a ton
crucial number most crucial number five
thousand five thousand one hundred
rupees per ton you need to track that
number besides the numbers management
commentary
will be key as well back to you nigel
thanks a lot for joining us and giving
us all those details well that slight
recovery is also coming in because of
icici bank that stock is
of the low point of the day and the
company will and the bank will be
posting its results over the weekend
abhishek kothari is standing by to take
us through the estimates abhishek over
to you
well it's going to be a good set of
numbers as per analyst expectation for
icsf bank
the key things to watch is that bank has
raised about three thousand one hundred
off-road
through stakes in subsidiaries so that
should provide question
on the net interest margin front now
philip capital estimates slippages of
about 3800 crores
this compares to q4 number of 5306 crore
now the moratorium one uh that book was
a thirty percent of the total loans so
that movement will be seen very closely
the lower rated or double b a lower
rated book that was close to sixteen
thousand six seventy crores
uh forming about two point six percent
of the book how much slippage is coming
from that
will be seen uh very closely uh cuts in
nclr uh rates
should uh provide uh some cut in their
yields also
however provisions are expected to
remain elevated as well
uh so for our polls we expect and i have
growth of 15 and a half percent on a
wi-fi business
while net profit to rise by 40 percent
on a wi-fi basis practice
okay abhishek thanks a lot for joining
us and giving us what to expect from
icici bank remember the bank reports
numbers tomorrow that is on a saturday
a quick look at the markets nifty still
down around 70 odd points we have the
bank nifty which is down 2
and what is causing this decline is
icici bank we have sbi also which is not
doing so well in trade today
apart from that do keep an eye out on z
entertainment the company reports its
numbers tomorrow the stock is down
around 400 percent
but it is expected to be a week quarter
this time around because of declining ad
revenues
apart from that we have indulgo which is
also declining in trade around three and
a half percent down right now
bharti infra reporting its numbers on
monday that stock 2 is seeing a decline
of 3 odd percent
but with that it's a wrap on this
edition of mid cap radar your stocks
when we return stay tuned to cnbc